[ED]
Thank you for watching!
That's what I'm talking about.
Excuse me.
Once again, we are...
We are Shrimp Dance.
We're here to announce the midterm results of the EbiDance Dream Match.
We will be announcing the interim results of the EbiDance Dream Match!
We can't wait to announce the results, but we're really looking forward to it!
The Evidan Dream Match is now underway, and I'd like to explain what kind of project it is.
Let me explain again what kind of project it is.
New Day New Wave
Ebidan Yamanote Line Jack
As part of the Haruta Tsuruta Ebidanza Project
We are actually the unit for each station
New Day New Wave, a total of 27 versions for each station have been released!
The unit that was listened to a lot among those 27 stations
The unit that has been listened to the most will appear on the stage at this year's EBIDAN the Live 2023!
Please listen to the music of the unit you want to see on stage and support them!
We would like to see a lot of Japanese trends on social networking sites, so please use the hashtag EBIDANSO!
We would be very happy if you could tweet us with the hashtag EBIDANZA LIVE 2023!
Thank you very much!
Let's start from the third place!
Third place goes to
This team!
This is quite surprising.
Here we go.
The Jim Brothers.
Oh!
Safe travels, brothers.
First place.
You were right, we were in first place.
No way. Third place.
This is quite fun!
It's fun.
And then
From here, first place, second place...
Yes, sir.
I'm curious.
How do you have different siblings?
The second place is...
They're so cute.
cute
picnic
Delicious
comfortable to open
Next, articulate
This one has a lot of Emiran members on it.
I see.
Please, by all means, try to find the one you are looking for.
Yes, sir.
Yes, yes...
That's great.
Roulette.
Want to play? Mr. John.
I'd like to play.
May I?
I'll make it special.
Oh, well, here you go.
Something for the weather.
Oh, is it over?
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Let's do it again.
This way.
From the beginning.
Max level.
Yes, sir.
It's so fast.
So there are levels.
This is it.
Hmm?
Who's there?
Oh! It's Mr. Leopard Man.
Oh!
Yes!
I won, Mr. Leopard Man.
And now...
I have a big announcement to make.
Big announcement?
A big announcement.
First and second place in the Ebi-dan Dream Match.
And the team that could be ranked in the extra perfect prize
will be on stage at this year's Ebirai.
What is it like to be on stage?
To be on stage?
Performing?
Are those three groups going to get some kind of award?
Ahh...
Sure, sure.
A medal or something.
AwardsCommendations
First
Boo-boo.
Ah.
No, sir.
Uh ...
what is it?
Oh, maybe...
Shuffle units?
Or a shuffle unit?
booboo!
Uh-oh.
No?
I don't know.
What else do you think?
What else? The other?
The other?
What do you think it is?
Yes!
Oh, what?
Uh...
I've got some really good food here.
Boo-boo.
Uh...
What else? Other?
What?
Well, you know, they say there's a big hippopotamus and rice paddies.
Making rice paddies.
What? What? What?
Which one do I get?
What?
Make it?
At the concert.
Live?
Llama live.
What are you talking about?
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
It's not important.
What do you mean?
I was wondering when.
The other one isn't.
And now, I'd like to make an announcement.
I'm here to announce the team of Mr. Branch Stretcher.
At Ebidan's Alive 2023.
We'll be putting out an original unit song.
We'll be releasing an original unit song.
Wow!
That's great!
As for the Pitari Prize
3rd to 12th place
In terms of votes, this is the left half.
We will announce the Pitari Prize winners on Saturday, May 13th.
We will announce the winner on Saturday, May 13th
We will announce it live on Saturday, May 13th when the results are announced.
If you finish in the top 12
you will have a chance to win the Pitari Prize!
Unit songs and so on.
There are some combinations of members that can only be achieved at this time.
There will be a combination of members that can only be achieved
I'm sure there will be a combination of members that can only be achieved at this time.
If you have any strategies based on all of the above, please let us know.
If you have any strategies, please add them to the hashtag
Please tweet about it with the hashtag
I would be very happy if you could tweet about it
I'd be happy to hear from you!
I heard a rumor...
I heard a rumor that you have a cold.
Are you okay? You said you delivered.
Just to test it out.
Just to try it out.
Try it out.
What is it?
You know, you were talking about this earlier.
12th place.
Usudani.
The Ori team, right?
Yes.
Who's with who?
Me?
A.
I don't know. A...
On Instagram... in my story.
It's like a white notebook and a...
and hamsters are similar.
Something like that.
"A" was posting a story like that.
I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I'm just guessing.
He's selfish, isn't he?
Ha-ha-ha-ha.
Maybe.Maybe.
Maybe.
I think he thinks you're a hamster.
What?
In that case...
Solo.
You want to see it solo?
Solo or...
Sort of.
I see.
Karma's a bitch.
Fake.
Ha-ha-ha-ha-ha.
I see.
Well...
You mind if I go the other way?
Even if it's just one person.
On a solo stage.
I think it's fine.
So...
I don't know.
I don't know without an explanation from him.
I don't know, but there are rumors
I don't know.
I'm sure you'll be interested in that, too.
I hope everyone will pay attention to it.
I'm hoping that everyone will pay attention to it.
I'm really...
I hope it's white text.
I hope it's not a hamster.
How about you, Ei-kun?
I'm scared.
That's scary...
Okay, then... the last one...
I've just left...
Let's all close with that word
Let's all close with that word.
Let's do it.
That's right.
Thank you very much.
Yes, sir.
Please.
Now what do we do with this?
Yes, of course.
It's already started.
Yes, please.
Okay, then.
Please.
Well, we're almost there.
All right, all right, all right.
Hour Club YouTube.
I'm Ebidan. Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you. - Nice to meet you.
Finally!
The Ebidan Dream Match is now underway.
I'd like to explain again what kind of project it is.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry.
I'll pick it up once.
I think we should stop for a moment.
I'd better stop for a moment.
And the delivery.
And the delivery itself, please stop.
Excuse me, sir.
Can you shake this camera?
Yes, sir.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Wait a minute.
What's going on?
Can you get this on? Here.
Hey. - What?
What? Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Hey, it's not on right now.
Is it on right now?
I didn't even notice.
Let's do this.
Don't do that.
I didn't even notice.
That's you two.
What the hell are you doing?
What are you doing?
No, no, no, no, no.
Kirova, you have no idea what you're doing.
I'm totally guessing.
Okay, well...
I think the lights are in the wrong place.
What? I really didn't notice.
Accident, accident, accident, accident, accident.
Okay, I'll keep going.
It's a little hazy right now.
Through the camera.
Over the axis.
You're nodding your head.
What's wrong with me?
I've seen your story and everything.
I just got a new job.
You've been going to live shows, right?I think he's been going around to live shows.
Oh, okay.
Shall we continue?
Now, I'm curious about the rankings.
Yes, sir.
Let's get to it.
The 13th place is as follows.
Please.
Please do.
Uno, please.
I really didn't have anything.
Wow.
Yes, sir.
But I didn't expect that...
Ungui Sudari...
Well, you know, surprisingly, you were already in thirteenth place.
Bird... bird... bird...
Bird... bird... bird... bird... bird...
The bird...
There's a possibility of a solo show.
Yes, the possibility of a solo live performance is important
And now for the second place!
The unanimous No. 1!
Brothers Mejiro Station.
Wow.
I didn't expect this.
There's been a move.
Down.
That's a down move.
Oh, but up one.
Up, up.
It's upse up.
It's upse up, right?
Up.
Last time I was here, I was in third place.
That's what I thought.
Sticky.
And first place!
Stylish Harajuku Station and
Wow!
Stylish!
Thank you very much!
Here it is.
Here's a close-up.
It's gone.
Make sure you get a good look at it.
Is there such a thing as a wallet?
Shape-memorize it.
I don't think so.
Remember... it's up.
It's up.
Looks like there's been quite a change in the rankings.
That's a lot.
Yeah.
There's something called "Sawyer Roulet.
It's on Ebidan TikTok.
Yes, there is.
I'm going to try it this time.
I'm taking on this challenge.
Yes...
Last time, you did it.
Yes, I did.
I'm the max.
This is how he chooses who to be with.
I'm sorry.
No, no, no, no.
I got it, I got it, I got it.
I got it, I got it, I got it, I got it.
There it is.
What the fuck?
That's...
It's hard to get a good shot.
You can't even aim.
I covered it in Ebidan The Parade.
I see.
Is there any song you would like to cover?
Like I said before...
I've done almost all of the shuffles.
I've done all of them.
So...
I wonder...
I don't know, but...
Buddy's...
And there's no sakura shimeji mushrooms.
Ah...
There are no sakura shimeji mushrooms.
You said that too.
You're looking at me like I'm hot.
That's why I've never done it before.
There are so many groups.
I'd like to try it.
That's true.
How about you, Sakura Shimeji?
Ha-ha-ha.Ha-ha-ha.
Oh, no.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
It's not a picture.
It's not a regular meal.
So, if you were to join Evidan...
Is there a group you'd like to join?
If there is, can I let you know?
Ebidan.
I'm sure there is.
You simply don't hear it.
I'm kind of in the middle of something really serious right now.
I'm focused.
I'm concentrating.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry.
That's all.
With Milk Yamanaka and Nakataro.
The game is on me, with Ryota Nakano
Ryuhei Sasaki and
Yoshifuchi Sasaki.
Tetsuya
The end
The End
I was remembering Lucky.
The end.
with Hiroki Tanaka of Super Dallon
Seiya of Buddy's and
Haruki and
and Yuki of Buddy's
Thank you very much
I am Takashi Tanaka of Trump and
Assistant Director Hiroshi Takatani.
I'm not very excited.
No, no, no, no.
Don't come in.
Why are you coming in now?
If it's Evidan...
I want to be in the acting section.
Now?
I'm happy now, but...
I'm glad you're here.
I've been thinking about it for a long time, haven't I?
Jisaku, Jisaku, Jisaku.
I've been thinking about it for a long time
Why did you come?
I came back from Sendai today.
That's where I came from.
I just got back.
So...
I'm working on it.
I was going to tell her to go, but she said...
I was going to tell you to go on with your day, but you said you were streaming.
I'll be your cameraman.
That's funny.
That's amazing.
It's the second day!
You're not busy, are you?
No, I'm not bored.
Busy, busy, busy.
Bullshit.
You're lying!
You're busy
He's been behind me the whole time.
Thank you Ginny Shirai too!
That's why
I'd like to end with that word pose
I'd like to end with that word pose.
Please join me.
Seino
That's what I'm talking about.
Thank you very much.
I'm just now getting grizzled.
I hope that's all right.
Okay, so we're live now.
We are...
We are Ebidan.
I'm sorry, I'm sorry, let's do it again.
When we say it, you all say it.
Let's do it!
We are...
We are EBIDAN!
We're here to announce the final ranking.
This is the last one, no matter if you're crying or laughing.
Twenty-seventh place.
This is the last time, no matter if you cry or laugh
Third place, Sanbori Station.
Congratulations! Thank you for putting it up.
No.26, Anytime Main Building Atmosphere
25th place, Dessert Okachimachi station25th , Dessert Okachimachi station
24th, Bado Takadanobaba station
23rd, Komagoma station
No.22, Pisces Shinagawa station
No.21, Naga-Yurakucho station
Damn!
How is it?
Well, well, well, well.
This is good, too.
It's frustrating, isn't it?
You're supposed to have a bigger reaction.
Don't say it!
I have a habit of going out a lot.
Wow, that's frustrating!
I'm so sorry.
Too big!
No. 20, Basketball Shibuya station
No. 19, Anime Ikebukuro station
Yay!
Damn!
I did it!
No. 18, Bird-Umiyatani station
Solo?
Not solo?
It's Hiro's solo project again.
Let's hear some details!
Let's hear some details.
I'm sorry.
Please explain.
I didn't buy the text.
What?
Why did I do that?
What about the birds?
I'm on the bird team.
You were asked in the survey.
Have you ever bought a bird?
I said, "I buy them with confidence!
I said, "I'm confident about it!
It was a hamster, wasn't it?
I did buy a hamster.
Is it similar?
Well, this one does.
That's impossible.
You're right.
Now, let's move on to No. 17...
Koshinmachi Otsuka Station
Oh!
16th place
Ramen Tamachi station
Wow!
Mizu Urai Confectionery Station
What?
How many are in here?
How many of these are in there?
There's about 6 in here.
There's only about two.
Why aren't there four?
No. 15
Tetta Shinbashi station
Oh!
Sogo...
Sogo-kun and I
A two-person unit
We got a pretty good ranking.
14th place
Study Yoyogi Station
Oh!
I'm in there too!
Study Yoyogi station
Damn!
You look great.
You really like studying?
Say "damn".
Damn!
Say "fuck"!
Like a whore.
How to say hobu.
One group left
13th place
Tabata station with rice field
Oh!
I did too.
12th place
Who's that?
Hanryugetsu Shin-Okubo station
Oh!
And 11th place
Granny's Child Sugamae Station
Oh!
There's a lot of them.
Too many
So many.
Grandma, lots of grandma's?
No, no, no.
You can see it in this one.
No, you don't.
Number 10.
Leader, Shinjuku Station.Leader Shinjuku Station
Oh!
Excellent people.
Takuya Imada, not even one.
Oooh!
Ninth place.
Adventure, Mitsubouchi Station
Yes!
Oh!
I'm so happy!
8th place.
Senior Osaki station
Oh!
Osawa
There's a good man.
There is.
Let's announce... Seventh place.
Drawing Ueno Station
Oh!
Honorable Mention
Honorable Mention.
There are so many!
Sixth place.
Who didn't write their name?
The name of the salt Hamamatsuyu station
The name of the salt, Hamamatsuyu station
Oh!
Fifth place.
Idol Akiyama station
Oh!
Who is it?
Idol
A lot of idols!
There's so many!
Fourth place.
Fashionable Harajuku Station
Oh!
Stylish!
Good!
In third place
Good eye, Meguro station
Good wish
good, good
it's good, it's good, it's good
This one is already here
I'm waiting, or rather, I haven't been called yet.
Confirmed
This is Unit 2.
This is an original unit song.
It's a production and distribution release.
The ranking is
We have first and second place, so we'll start with second place.
Wouldn't first place be better?
Wouldn't second place be better?
You don't have to announce it.
You have three choices.
Second place first, or first place first?
Sorry.
What a pain in the ass!
Second place.
Okay, okay.
Second place is
2nd place is
Understandable position
Nishinishippori station from western Japan
Yay
Yay!
why not?
Just in case
I'm from Tokushima!
I don't fall into that category, do I?
No one in western Japan thought of me.
To the western Japanese.
I'm an alien.
I'm not an alien.
That's all right.
Well, I'll tell you what.
Number one, as you all know.
Number one is the brothers.
Oh, my God, oh, my God, oh, my God.
Congratulations.
Congratulations, sir. - Congratulations, sir.
Congratulations, sir.
Why did it have to be me?
Was it there?
Congratulations
First and second place...
It's amazing, isn't it, the original unit's
Production and distribution release
That's great.
Congratulations!
Now, I'd like to ask a question to the members
I'd like to ask you a question.
First of all, I'd like to start with the second place, from Nishinippo Station.
I've already spent the rest of my term
I've already spent the rest of this term in the west of Japan.I put it all on West Japan.
All of it.
I put it all on West Japan.
I really did.
Thanks to everyone's help.
I think it's Cos.
I'm really proud of it.
I can write new songs
I'm really looking forward to singing with everyone
In a way, it's like...
It's like a collaboration between Charm and Super Express.
I don't think it's an exaggeration to say that.
I'm looking forward to that too.
So please look forward to it.
Thank you very much.
Congratulations!
Three more to go for such a big one.
Now, let's see if we can find some flies.
First place, Mejiro Station.
Congratulations!
Congratulations, sir.
How was it?
I knew it!
It's amazing.
I never thought I'd be on stage with all these brothers.
I never thought I'd be on stage with these brothers.
I'm a little nervous now.
but I think it's a rare opportunity for us to get to know each other.
I'm going to play an original song.
Please look forward to it.
Thank you very much.
Naoyama?
I'm going to make it bad.
He said bad things.
You're late.
You can use me either way.
Shoot.
Chute.
Chutes.
Brother and sister team
Light Dive
As for Loveya.
It's true.
I'm really very
I'm very grateful, and
Last year, wasn't it?
Last year, right?
After Dish graduated.
When the timing was right.
I said, "Let's sell the shrimp band.
And you know...
The Jidai Project has grown so big
I could feel that the project has grown so big
I could feel the support of everyone.
I wanted to return the favor
I'd like to return the favor on stage.
Thank you so much!
It's wonderful.
From here
I'm going to decide on the "plus one" prize.
I'm trying to decide
How do you decide?
I'm having a little bit of trouble deciding.
I'm having a bit of a hard time deciding.
Kevin.
What do you think is best?
I guess...
How about a raffle?
Everyone raffles.
You suck at raffles.
I'm thinking of doing it this way.
I'm going to decide.
Are you sure these girls are...
BNR.
I don't know.
Who are you guys?
You must be Lienel, who debuted on April 29th
Lienel, who made her debut on April 29th at the shrimp dance parade.
We are
We are Rienel.
We will be your helpers today.
We look forward to working with you.
You'll see a space at the bottom of this page.
Here.
Starting with the person in third place.
You can put a sticker anywhere you like.
Please put a sticker anywhere you like.
And then you can choose a letter to put on the sticker.
And then we will choose a letter of the alphabet...
Which letter of the alphabet you choose
which letter of the alphabet to choose?
The word "Sawyer" means "red", so
The representative of red
Yuki Senpai
Representative of Red
Representative of red
I would like to ask Yuki to draw.
I'm going to let my ego out a little bit and use Jutaro's J.A little ego-boosting, with a J-taro J.
That's good.
Let's let our egos out!
It's "SOYA".
Type B, so a little B.
It's so personal.
Which one shall we choose?
There's only one thing left.
Soccer.
Soccer is the only choice.
But...
Jutaro why J?
No, no, no.
What happens if you go to an open spot?
Okay, all the teams are done.
Order of Doom.
Seriously, this is going to change our destiny.
I want to change fate with my own hands.
Normally, we'd all be like, "Whoa! I'd be all like...
I like the blue one.
I like it.
The last one.
The man of destiny.
Last one, please.
Use your best voice.
Destiny.
I'm your destiny.
You're gonna have to change that.
That's pretty polite.
Very polite.
From there?
From the start?
I don't know why it's frizzy.
I feel lost.
I don't know.
Is this okay?
It's fine.
It went pretty well.
If you could just mess it up.
Drumroll, please.
I'll do it.
I'm ready.
Okay.
That's it!
Here we go.
What do you mean, "Let's go"?
I'll do it.
You can check.
G
So...
Mr. Kai.
Even if you pull a G1000...
What happens?
What happens now?
Let me see what's down there.
All right, camera guys, come with me.
Follow me, please.
Slowly. Slowly.
Here we go.
What's going on?
I don't remember.
I don't have a choice.
I'm scared. I'm scared.
I'm gonna draw 1,000.
I'm going this way.
I'm going diagonally.
He's gone.
Hey! Hey!
Where are you?
I think we've found the perfect prize.
Please.
Okay.
C.
Oh!
Yes!
All right, all the appropriate members, please step forward.
please go to the front.
A word
Mr. Kai.
I'm very happy to be here.
Senior?
He's my senior.
I'm so glad you're here.
I was chosen for the Anti-Pollution Love Team.
I was chosen for the Anti-Fluxe team, so I'm going to play a really cool song
and stuff.
If you're going to go to the trouble of making a song that's really
K-pop, or something like that
I'd be happy to play such a song
I'd be happy to do it.
I wonder if Hayato and Hyoma are in the band?
I hope we can make a cool song.
I'm looking forward to it!
Congratulations!
2nd place Nejiro station
2nd Nishinippori station
3rd place, Shin-Okubo station
The Pitari PrizeThe Pitari Prize
Shin-Okubo Station
Brothers from West Japan and
Anti-stream lover
These three units are
Which timing?
I was watching the timing like that.
I kind of lost track of the timing.
I'm sorry.
These are the three units.
We've been working on an original unit song.
We're going to create and distribute our own original unit song.
They will perform on stage at Beyond the LIME 2023.
On stage at Beyond the LIME 2023.
And finally...
I have an exciting announcement to make to you all.
That's right.
Just in time.
May I say something?
Can I say it?
I don't know if it's okay.
Can I say it or not?
Let's put it to a vote.
Mellow, mellow, mellow
Those who think it's okay to say it
I think it's okay to say it
Is this the right place?
You've all been acting like idiots for the past month or so.
Idiot!
Finally...
NEW DAY NEW WAVE music video will be
May 16th.
That's 3 days from now.
It will be released on Tuesday at 9:00 p.m.
So everyone, let's end with that word...
Let's end with those words.
Let's end with that word.
Don't worry about it.
Let's just get it right.
Let's do it.
Let's go.
Ready?
That's great.
Thank you very much.